

PROFILE

I began my professional technical work with Best Buy's Geek Squad. Since then, I have worked on projects that have taught me coding and communication skills, project management, marketing and ultimately helped me grow a love for technology and the internet.

As a member of the Eleven Fifty Academy alumni, it is my goal to use the skills I have acquired to build a successful career as a developer. Please contact me to discuss your company vision and values. Let me show you how I can be an asset to your team.

CONTACT

PHONE: (765)717-1913

WEBSITE:

www.linkedin.com/in/chellemo

EMAIL:

Chellemo23@gmail.com

MICHELLE SMITH

Android and Web Developer

SKILLS

Languages: Java, JavaScript, Kotlin, HTML5, CSS3

Libraries: React, JSON, ¡Query, Angular, Bootstrap, Express.js,

Socket.IO, Node.js, Retrofit

Development: GitHub, Postgres, MongoDB Atlas, Postman,

Heroku

Text Editors: Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ Idea, Android Studio

Professional: Problem Solving, Project Management, Marketing,

Collaboration, Content Management, Social

Media

EDUCATION

Eleven Fifty Academy

March 2019 – August 2019 Full Stack JavaScript Developer Certificate

Udemy

Android Developer Certification (Completed: February 2020) Kotlin programming course (Currently enrolled)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Real Otaku Gamer, Indie Games Contact Manager

January 2011-January 2012

Point of contact for indie game developers wanting to advertise their products on the Real Otaku Gamer website, writer, editor

Pink and Deadly Co-founder, Co-producer

October 2009-October 2010

Co-founder and co-host of the Pink and Deadly video game podcast

Best Buy, Counter Intelligence Agent

August 2006–March 2009

Bench technician, computer repair, customer service, sales

PROJECTS

Christmas Cookie Jar

May 2019

A cookie recipe app built with React App where users can log in and add their favorite cookie recipes and find recipes added by others. This was my Blue Badge level project for Eleven Fifty Academy

Christmas Cookie Jar

GitHub

My Repositories